Guide to the Gordon Grand Fellowship at Yale University Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Gordon Grand Fellowship at Yale University records
1976-1994
RU 311
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2.75
The records consist of correspondence, reports, schedules, printed material and audio cassettes documenting the Gordon Grand Fellowship at Yale University.
Yale University. Office of the Secretary
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 4-A (YRG 4-A), Records of the Yale secretary's office.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, reports, schedules, printed material and audio cassettes documenting the Gordon Grand Fellowship at Yale University.
Business -- Scholarships, Fellowships, etc.; Lectures and lecturing; Audiotapes; Gordon Grand Fellowship; Yale University. Council of Masters; Yale University. Office of the Secretary
- Records of the lecture coordinator on the Gordon Grand lectures, 1976-1994; Accession 1997-A-071
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2028
  - Nonvich Goodspeed, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Nominees, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Invitees (2nd semester), 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bronfman, 1987 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Brandon Tartikoff NBC, 1988 February 2-3 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Brochure, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Serg Trigano Club Med, 1990 April 10 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Nominees, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Stanley Goldstein Melville Corp, 1991 April 4 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Robert E. Allan AT&T, 1991 November 12 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Thomas W. Tusher, Levi Strauss Co., 1994 October 30-31 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Gordon Grand Bills--paid (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Declinations Bahrige, lacocca, Ropest, Spielberg, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Program General & Financial, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Gordon Grand General, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Declinations Smith Gray Blumenthd., 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Fellowship Annual Report, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Financial, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Col Frank Borman (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Bruce Jenner (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - General Report, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - David Jones Humana, 1985 October 9-10 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Berry Gordy (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - General, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Annual Report General, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Bills, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Turner Volker Declination, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Annual Report 1987-88; Annual Report 1988-89; Annual Report 1986-1987; SOM (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Gordon Grand Misc; Financial, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Misc Gordon Grand (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Declinations, Waliker McCartel Smith Pfeiffers, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - General, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Liz Claiborne, 1989 April 17-18 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - History Old Speakers (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Gordon Grand Scheduling (Box 2, Folder 88)
- Correspondence, schedules, printed material, and audiocassettes of Gordon Grand Lecture Series, 1984-1985; Accession 2000-A-032 (Box 1)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2020
  Scope and Contents
  No inventory available.
  - Promoting Economic Growth and Competitiveness, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Berry Gordy, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gordon Grand fellowship, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)